JENNIFER KONG

10244 Danskin Dr., Las Vegas, NV 89166 · 702.714.0392 kong.jenewa@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-m-kong

OBJECTIVE

Over 20 years experience in hospitality, seeking to break into the IT sector. Recently completed an associate's in Network Security, specializing in Cyber Security. Knowledge of various network protocols and security practices. Extensive experience with Cisco networking devices and protocols. Versed in Linux.

EXPERIENCE

FEBRUARY 2005 - PRESENT

GUEST SERVICES REPRESENTATIVE, SUNCOAST HOTEL & CASINO - LAS VEGAS, NV

Responsible for greeting guests, parking and retrieving cars in a safe and timely manner, assisting with guests' luggage, coordinating with bell service, being a source of information on various matters such as transport. Frequent accolades in customer service program.

OCTOBER 2010 - MARCH 2021

EVENTS COORDINATOR, KORABO TAIKO - LAS VEGAS, NV

Helped create Korabo Taiko in 2010. Responsibilities included, but not limited to: creating a cohesive graphic identity, designing an official website, marketing, managing the financial aspects of the company, and leading a team of volunteers. After the initial company setup, upkeep responsibilities included: managing correspondence between clients and volunteers, event booking, performer scheduling, public relations, website upkeep, marketing, and finances.

OCTOBER 2002 - DECEMBER 2004

STUDENT HELPER I, STATE OF HAWAI'I LEGISLATIVE - REFERENCE BUREAU & DEPARTMENT OF TRANSPORTATION (AIRPORTS DIVISION) - HONOLULU, HI

Responsibilities included greeting and advising visitors, managing various filing systems, delivering and receiving packages, and other administrative assistant tasks.

EDUCATION

FALL 2018 - SPRING 2021

ASSOCIATE OF APPLIED SCIENCE IN NETWORK SECURITY - CYBER SECURITY

COLLEGE OF SOUTHERN NEVADA

FALL 2007 - SPRING 2012

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS; ART HISTORY MINOR

UNIVERSITY OF NEVADA, LAS VEGAS

SKILLS

- CCNA
- TCP/IP
- Network+, Security+

- LAN, WAN
- Router/ Switch
- Linux